U.S. Department of Labor Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee #16 Records 5325
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Department of Labor Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee #16 Records
1954
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Department of Labor U.S. Department of Labor. Wage and Hour Division.
5325
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Official report of proceedings before the Wage and Hour Division of the U.S. Department of Labor, in the matter of: Special Industry Committee Number 16-A for Puerto Rico to investigate conditions and recommend minimum wages for certain industries.
5971760
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 08, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 11, 2019
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of the official report of proceedings before the Wage and Hour Division of the U.S. Department of Labor, in the matter of: Special Industry Committee Number 16-A for Puerto Rico to investigate conditions and recommend minimum wages for certain industries. The proceedings took place in October and November 1954, in Santurce, Puerto Rico.
This collection does not contain the report of proceedings in its entirety.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5320: U.S. Department of Labor Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division 5321: U.S. Department of Labor Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee #12 Records 5322: U.S. Department of Labor Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee #13 Records 5323: U.S. Department of Labor Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee #14 Records 5324: U.S. Department of Labor Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee #15 Records 5326: U.S. Department of Labor Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee #31 Records
United States. Department of Labor; United States. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division. Special Industry Committee 16.; United States. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division.
5971760
- Official report of proceedings, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  October 19, 1954
- Official Report of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  October 20, 1954
- Official Report of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  October 20, 1954; volume 2 of 2
- Official Report of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  October 25, 1954
- Official Report of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  October 26, 1954
- Official Report of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  October 27, 1954
- Official Report of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  October 28, 1954
- Official Report of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  November 1, 1954
- Official Report of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  November 2, 1954
- Official Report of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  November 3, 1954
- Official Report of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  November 4, 1954
- Official Report of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  November 5, 1954
- Official Report of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  November 12, 1954
- Official Report of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  November 8, 1954
- Official Report of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  November 9, 1954
- Official Report of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  November 10, 1954
- Official Report of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  November 11, 1954